[Music]
[音乐]
the europeans have island in found some
欧洲人在发现一些岛屿
food security brilon 12 hours of work of
食品安全布里隆12小时的工作时间
today is it discovered her hobby speak
今天是不是发现了她的业余爱好
about so wonderful heard of nature
关于大自然的美妙回忆
methods have article news or last
方法有文章新闻或最新消息
dance for example the paper specialties
舞蹈，例如纸类专业
papers the latest story and the city is
报道最新的故事，这座城市是
to data into the proper database says
数据到正确的数据库说
a dealer use of data and
经销商使用数据和
relationships this is the team of facing
关系，这是面对的团队
side of here for example in finance
例如在金融方面
for Ford action for research and
福特行动的研究和
treatment whitmans telcos water are
治疗惠特曼电信公司水是
network and what happens to Mars
网络以及火星发生了什么
database of nature asked the giant times
自然数据库问大时代
like air from the cad on just database
就像来自CAD的空气一样
but that platform rejected me
但是那个平台拒绝了我
in workflows can handle like child cluster
在工作流中可以像子集群一样处理
et cetera spring creek resources as well
等等Spring Creek的资源
Knowledge becomes honorable editions
知识成为荣誉版
So photograph certain supply and
因此拍摄一定的供应和
database if the place to the website where
数据库是否放置在网站所在的位置
to make you work mors mors all the way to
让您一整天都在工作
work you have a mindset concept of mind
工作中你有心态观念
set bvs data ivo just use to lick
设置bvs数据ivo仅用于舔
turned bases of you are people and
你们的基础是人，
applications photographer from the national team
国家队的应用摄影师
what they started to think in graphs in
他们开始在图表中思考什么
notebooks document of might be
的笔记本文件可能是
good case use case for having a database
有数据库的好案例用例
database ec bathroom nauheim connected to do
数据库ec nauheim连接浴室
not have salons of data connector
没有沙龙的数据连接器
Wissing and makes sense of the state of
细细了解状态
data
数据
speak we are talking about winning the plaid
说我们正在谈论赢得格子呢
the based in reading car at the oscars
奥斯卡读书车的基础
is the fcz fans in the first motto
第一个座右铭是fcz粉丝
Make sense of the state and have to
了解状态，必须
management
管理
collect together major companies
汇聚大公司
appearance
看
the core business models but to benefit
核心业务模式却受益
of the data security autumn place in some
一些数据安全领域的秋季
other data base or penalty area
其他数据库或罚款区域
a car club of databases
汽车数据库俱乐部
think about when i speak about the database
想想我何时谈论数据库
databases pretty simple and focus on the
数据库非常简单，专注于
contents of science and africa lucky
科学和非洲的内容幸运
developed enough to black label
足够发展到黑标
alone this labels otto group the
仅此标签底部组
gentlemen the entire staff
全体员工先生们
the staff gap properties we can
我们可以提供的人员缺口
just add some things that looks like
只需添加一些看起来像
jason the motto bio is a business
杰森的座右铭生物是一家企业
case super from now on know windows
从现在开始超级案例Windows
Mr property of persons of the pacific
太平洋先生的财产
games always database and relationship
游戏总是数据库和关系
care to hectic properties what is
关心忙碌的财产是什么
personal hotspot contact now law
个人热点立即联系法律
for the mesh of connection is created
用于创建连接网格
at the monte carasso harrislee sizing
在蒙特卡洛斯·哈里斯利上浆
since 1
从1开始
people's here the boss interested in
人们在这里感兴趣的老板
great because you can not get enough and
很好，因为你不能得到足够的
feel the cover it is long was just
感觉很长的封面只是
do it because of the folk music stars
因为民间音乐明星而做
and rock n soul based my day
摇滚我的灵魂
become image of the database of you
成为您数据库的图像
speak about data access of articles
谈论文章的数据访问
at open source development project 10 1
在开源开发项目10 1
percent of the century and get is not
世纪的百分比
only that but for use cases
仅此而已，但针对用例
after kate maleike web platform
在kate maleike网站平台之后
The first runner or patch park
第一赛跑者或补丁公园
project sword caps days which use your
使用您的项目的剑帽天
work lotti or the hev in new haven
工作洛蒂或纽黑文中的混合动力车
which park analyzer services got
哪些公园分析仪服务有
doubt if the home back that
怀疑家里是否支持
coliseum sings
体育馆唱歌
about the title track like just too founded
关于标题轨道，就像刚刚成立一样
be x-lite turntables zealous in
热情的X-lite转盘
your baltimore complex from internet
您的巴尔的摩综合大楼，来自互联网
researcher lawrence lessig ski art as well
研究员劳伦斯·莱西格（Lawrence Lessig）也是滑雪艺术
presence youth for example the connection
存在青年，例如联系
peter king of pop otz pp the us persons
彼得·波兹之王pp美国
or persons autonomy in the hen first
或母鸡自主权
bring that is fine
带来很好
the
的
free dvd server or desktop
免费的DVD服务器或台式机
version live web browser now becomes the
版本的实时网络浏览器现在成为
cool of the very very graphic finally
最终非常酷的图形
could police of serengeti resources
塞伦盖蒂资源警察可以
Problems that most of the application 10
大多数应用程序存在的问题10
at the north header folder connect browser
在北头文件夹连接浏览器
put in the source
放入源
mostostal internet applications web
最新互联网应用程序网站
applications is a real database for
应用程序是一个真正的数据库
speakers of other three motors ford
其他三款福特汽车的扬声器
engine on connectivity she has as well
她也拥有连接性的引擎
and rock hard log fdp of water
和岩石硬日志fdp的水
first remote access protocol ip cores
第一个远程访问协议ip内核
ewald addition fdp görlitz libraries
埃瓦尔德（Ewald）加工厂FDP格尔利茨图书馆
she has origin of new jersey in
她来自新泽西
bed database solution station is
床数据库解决方案站是
Optimal is from North Hitting the garbage
最佳选择来自北方
collector too much ots connector for
收集器的ots连接器过多
Applications still wait and see
应用程序仍在观望
thanks for application crashes the time
感谢您的应用程序崩溃的时间
database crashes the database do there
数据库崩溃在那里做数据库
the emergency system and disk now in
应急系统和磁盘现在已放入
memory of heart toyoda
丰田心脏的记忆
so there is so much nortel is at
所以有很多北电
roast or search food if you want to
烧烤或寻找食物
work with what they used cars pejcic
与他们使用的汽车pejcic合作
obediently companies who you master of the
听话的你是谁掌握的公司
proxy firewall really loves to say what
代理防火墙真的很喜欢说什么
goes to use any more
去使用了
until 6 so worry the focus called bot
直到6，所以担心焦点叫做bot
about rottweil he is described choose
关于他描述的罗威
on support languages ​​of course java
关于课程Java的支持语言
python script to create this special
python脚本来创建这个特殊的
top3 bosco is first ever used it
top3 bosco首次使用它
Pull connector of students
学生拉连接器
so you see what that first
所以你先看看
implemented photo conny bosch
已实施的照片conny bosch
photography to recognize gatwick as
摄影承认盖特威克
amor friendly including java is
Amor友好，包括Java是
a crazy possible but i can use case
一个疯狂的可能，但我可以用例
the two so long is the fund so
这两个基金这么久
very much she hates connector either for
她非常讨厌连接器
active community continues from what like a
活跃的社区从像
like crosby grafs in scientific sometimes
有时像科学中的crosby grafs
had written
写过
[Music]
[音乐]
reads fdp hessen no further information
读取fdp hessen没有更多信息
it becomes complex by the missing some complex
由于缺少一些复杂而变得复杂
me in front of james space co body point
我在詹姆斯空间公司的身体前
special day date on which causes of
特殊原因的日期
to ask pointers et cetera
问指针等
Astor with band of using board
带使用板带的Astor
controls expectations apps like you
控制像您一样的期望应用
north is poker matic or xml way
北是扑克matic或xml方式
to define the domain stations and
定义域站并
Configuration will not be a system
配置将不是系统
auto.com configured driver the age
auto.com配置的驱动程序年龄
skinstad look into the pilot is mapping
skinstad看着飞行员正在映射
home look like to gp ltd
gp ltd的首页外观
like once on relationships but by
就像一次关系，但
simple goods help is not topmodel
简单的货物帮助不是顶级模特
Relationship in front of flat like college
像大学一样在公寓前的关系
relationship between properties
属性之间的关系
narrated was here before simple out
叙述在这里，然后简单出来
the interests of hessian puberty
黑森州青春期的利益
Skepticism part in book form at this time
怀疑论目前在书本形式中
topic this is mati seriously motto make
这是马蒂认真的座右铭
you do not want for example set topic
您不想例如设置主题
know that person's youtube and have any
知道那个人的youtube并拥有
beck to have just got
贝克刚刚得到
out of the box for example is star
开箱即用的是星星
weight watchers person like that and have that
体重观察者这样的人
motto if you like your configuration
座右铭，如果你喜欢你的配置
functionality we are session factory
我们是会话工厂的功能
that's the moment you open it when the
那是您打开它的那一刻
open session series connection works
公开课系列连接作品
tablet bumps database the half of
平板电脑颠簸数据库的一半
action express addiction lies down like
动作表达成瘾躺下来像
courses session can be decided
课程时间可以决定
but what should be used to the more
但是应该更多地使用
than one's transaction but it's the
比一个人的交易，但这是
possible so you think about the session
可能，所以您考虑会议
sms
短信
like obsession, it worked like data
就像痴迷一样，它就像数据一样工作
either solo to data for the mud
要么单打独斗的数据
forward because we all know what matters
前进，因为我们都知道重要
a single slot mother before you
之前有一个单槽妈妈
now working to the point and that is
现在工作到这一点，那就是
just complex want to see before my
只是复杂想在我之前看到
domain data in a state dubai customs
迪拜海关的域名数据
zeal of the place working on show and sing
表演和唱歌的地方的热情
still possible and slide principle
仍然可能和滑动原理
the armchair statement the not even
扶手椅说不
before the topic just came the person
在这个话题出现之前，那个人
who would need to make the border statement
谁需要做出边界声明
displays do care testing notices you
显示器进行保养测试会通知您
to force
力
offtopic so if you want to get all yours
脱口而出，所以如果你想得到你所有的
data that would be image in quality
高质量的图像数据
the costs
成本
ok us dollar base because he would say
好吧，美元基础，因为他会说
that is a waterproof project so are you
那是一个防水工程，你也是
on watch ronson e mail a move there
观看ronson向那里发送电子邮件
we have combine data access ends
我们结合了数据访问端
so now 10 2010 when she created the
现在是2010年10月，当她创建
first thing tvc tsx-v tgp apple sits
第一件事电视tsx-v tgp苹果坐
and if it includes station the benefits of use
如果它包括车站使用的好处
with something so loose on jews
犹太人身上松散的东西
bands up and jump data access who
捆绑并跳转数据访问者
is it domains
它是域
his focus posse tories was so for mohr
他的重点是保守
continent data access to not have to
大陆数据访问不必
but do sessions in fremont where to go
但是在弗里蒙特做会议去哪里
loud when sex we just to section on our
大声的性爱时，我们只是剖析我们
Unit of work we have in the best
我们拥有最好的工作单元
case you have used abstraction
如果您使用了抽象
in some cases complex cases you do not
在某些情况下，您不会
start sets this situation statements
开始设置此情况陈述
a notebook sound from the project that
项目中的笔记本声音
i had a like aerobic dance
我有跳有氧舞蹈
So the sentences place where you get around
所以句子是你到处走的地方
Bad insights Morse complex business
不好的见解摩斯复杂的业务
analytics gravis you can not express 2
您无法表达的分析无权2
you do when you have this custom
当你有这个习惯时你会做
he designs the side as the best action
他把这边设计为最佳动作
photography patience that we have the curve
摄影耐心，我们有曲线
The cause of state of the data offers a
数据状态的原因提供了一个
concrete wall of the milieu but new case
环境的混凝土墙，但新案例
you like all through the works on
您喜欢所有的作品
spring data protector is very very
Spring 数据保护器非常非常
so much magic the 400 look deeper into
如此神奇的400看起来更深入
the framework is going on you just extent
该框架只是在某种程度上
to give it away victory is waiting
放弃胜利正在等待
that is definitely so wissing of
绝对是这样的渴望
switches do not want to save the station like that
交换机不想这样保存站
good as a fix
很好解决
also take over from team asset servicing
也接管团队资产服务
that's just wright interface message
那只是赖特界面消息
and not just surprised jörg of
而不仅仅是惊讶于
the box and put some nice soap on her
在盒子上放一些漂亮的肥皂
know that we ourselves in before and
知道我们自己之前和
return the whole love as well as to have
回报整个爱以及拥有
to return relationships becomes michael
返回关系成为迈克尔
Wirth of interest pois person topic
感兴趣的Pois人话题
connected with the baseballs
与棒球有关
European chip with models in Java
具有Java模型的欧洲芯片
domains as public as one can make sure
作为一个公共领域可以确保
that as far as first ship to
直到第一艘船
topic internet before you can
您可以先进行主题互联网
great down in create class in part
在部分创建类中表现出色
it's been - serbiens of the case you
这是-案件的塞尔维亚人
can express at a fair on one
可以在一个展览会上表达
participate in the fair
参加博览会
sat 1 it is advisable to checkout part obsolete
sat 1，建议检查部分过时
and could do so
并且可以这样做
edwards brings the dfb eleven
爱德华兹带来了dfb十一
that center management has been since you
自您以来，中心管理
now hope that nobody is so immediately you
现在希望没人会那么快
think 105 swing classical swing the
认为105秋千经典秋千
release train leave clock
释放火车离开时钟
that is her
那是她
the straight edge of space data model
空间数据模型的优势
and when is only good at the westring
而什么时候才最擅长
or takes all you can replays ix there
或带所有你可以在那里重播ix
I would have more too than managing risk
除了管理风险外，我还有更多
intelligence official community
情报官员社区
community motto work together to team
社区座右铭携手合作
with timo please michael cohrs willi
和蒂莫一起，迈克尔·科尔·威利
Scanning on to Japan's official release
扫描到日本的官方发行版
train is the theme so far that has been
火车是迄今为止的主题
before now, you'll be dripping
在此之前，你会滴
personals topic and the only one piece
交友主题和唯一的一件
the two men to be introduced
要介绍的两个人
construct the interlocking and owned
构建联锁和拥有
constructor got scotland people
建设者得到了苏格兰人
[Music]
[音乐]
negative as canon shift festival java
负，如佳能移位节java
and java solution wanted views of the
和Java解决方案想要的视图
good technology is in the spring
好技术在春天
framework goal shoots that solarworld
框架目标向太阳世界射击
name is to get the pieces constructor
名称是获取件构造函数
support moore into the people are
支持摩尔人
expected to behave the effectiveness of
期望表现出
flex in a lot of enemies a lot of bistro long
在很多小酒馆里招来很多敌人
we can not get into this but we
我们不能进入这个，但我们
think now went too far ahead of want to
认为现在远远超出了想要
Make people from youtube data office is
让YouTube数据办公室的人成为
The designer will be able to do it
设计师将能够做到
leads through data
引导数据
villepin for something more
villepin更多
what he do not leave out of the live
他没有离开现场的一切
door systems prize interview
门系统奖采访
tv star framework you are using so far
到目前为止使用的电视星空框架
on that statements in this case like that
在这种情况下的陈述
now wants complex statements
现在想要复杂的语句
expanded as far as slice of the time you
扩展到您所用时间的一小部分
want to create to know the ones on
想要创建以了解那些
course expected and also offers thrillers
当然课程，并提供惊险刺激
reads in a no more than eight
读入不超过8个
presence with more constant than
存在比
One hundred thousand focus on your used in
十万专注于您的习惯
this case some child of the charges of
这种情况下，一些孩子的指控
course the first certain mobile phone software
当然第一个特定的手机软件
domain model the know-center graf and
领域模型知识中心graf和
have three weeks and customs now too
现在也有三个礼拜和风俗
far data structure from you database but
数据结构离您的数据库远，但是
there's no way
没办法
you can do the soviet time north
你可以在北方做苏联时间
music was for playstation and josef
音乐是为playstation和josef设计的
zinses sometimes happy slapping stuff
zinses有时很高兴拍打东西
because they think we can do better
因为他们认为我们可以做得更好
even ask if they could be around
甚至问他们是否可以在附近
Reviews sun wrapping sometimes
有时评论防晒霜
Configuration of the piper on lake what
湖上吹笛者的配置是什么
does that for example the transaction
这样做例如交易
management section extract websession do
管理部分提取websession做
when you work and wonder why the
当你想知道为什么
transaction somehow ticked so
交易以某种方式打勾
as she is blond it is a bit
因为她是金发，所以有点
features off and be with her
和她在一起
we so it is still negative sorry he is
我们所以仍然很消极，对不起他
fallen in the hobby state using
陷入爱好状态
the early stage data and picture at first
首先是早期的数据和图片
Lucius how good it is vital and so far
Lucius到目前为止，它有多么重要
look like a simple examples of course
看起来像一个简单的例子
want to model large databases lot of
想要为大型数据库建模
tables before entire statements can get
整个语句之前的表
little bit complicated rossi as one way
一点点复杂的罗西作为一种方法
to put you load database nasa
让您加载数据库NASA
database
数据库
how far the community project is
社区项目有多远
officially supported as the power full
正式支持，功能强大
and one percent cares about that on board
百分之一的人关心船上的事情
to throw support for data from the sea
向海洋提供数据支持
obediently it goes from now to did it
从现在开始就顺从地做到了
it was said by breathless willingly sample
有人用呼吸困难的话说
complex picture into you connect or
连接到您的复杂图片或
tablets s1 of orcs on 14
14兽人的平板电脑s1
screenshot ottenbreit that they are exact
屏幕截图ottenbreit它们是精确的
sequel data base simyo base rtl tv today
今天的续集数据库simyo base rtl电视
is not the ships quickstart from swf
不是swf的船只快速入门
to know sandbox in the cloud
知道云中的沙箱
whatever you want to cervelo up to
无论您想做什么
easter tight youth click once upon a
复活节紧青年点击一次
database access data webbrowser on course
课程中的数据库访问数据Web浏览器
endbosse connection with any can
与任何罐头的endbosse连接
more application and connected
更多的应用程序和连接
you data provided for use
您提供的数据可供使用
Amon as a self-criticism clock now starts
阿蒙（Amon）作为自我批评的时钟现在开始
the party of time lab just as it was built
建立时间实验室的聚会
converteam part of the broadways support
百老汇支持的converteam部分
and support from one has vw activity of
并且来自大众的支持
performance of data under the website
网站数据的表现
the devil and application support for
魔鬼和应用程序支持
Coming out will effect this republic
出来将影响这个共和国
as well as on the course of the vw share but is not
以及大众分享的过程中，但不是
only awoke so wia i go to think we have
只是醒了，所以我去想我们有
go back to the world sports awards
回到世界体育大奖
bring her free for example the
例如让她自由
missing persons in the water and relying on
水中失踪人员并依靠
the water world but wants out of glass
水上世界，但想要玻璃杯
finding missions et cetera and spring
寻找使命等等
data kokoro common sense spring
数据kokoro常识春天
framework messerset is an objective like
框架Messengererset是一个目标，例如
second force base in the blocking way
第二力量基地的封锁方式
we want to support the fact that one
我们要支持以下事实：
that i want to work and focus more
我想工作并集中精力
finally the focused looks like the
最终聚焦的样子
first before
先于
patsy cline so everybody needs the
麻痹系，所以每个人都需要
newspaper configuration lures last
报纸配置引诱最后
what we have as you have mister
当你有先生时我们有什么
projector one reason is said they
投影机的一个原因是说他们
i did not have a database
我没有数据库
weitnau you can not willich start for
weitnau你不能willich开始
work like Hefner and institutional
像Hefner和机构一样的工作
got later as well as focus for immediate and
后来又着眼于立即和
she was for the sr at the expense of vips
她是为了高级而牺牲了vip
like all you need that looks pretty much
就像你所需要的一切一样
is true that but not in the domain of puberty
的确是这样，但不是在青春期
icesave watt moore is guidance for you
icesave瓦特摩尔为您提供指导
how to continents allowed
如何允许大洲
It is fire entire objective client
是火全客观客户
right now and get closer will be like that
现在，越来越近会像那样
kersting bit is optional mapping the
kersting位是可选的映射
Magic Lotto are looking forward to court soon
魔术乐透期待着不久上法庭
wheel to use the country already free
车轮使用该国已经免费
implementing siegwart functional tc3
实现siegwart功能tc3
a support at only for walking bass
仅在步行低音时提供支持
hollywood look system for walking in the
行走的好莱坞外观系统
case it may be mine
可能是我的
Objectives so pre-built in miniature
物镜如此微型化
support samba some people who are astorga
支持桑巴一些阿斯托加人
the family offices formspring data gpm
家族办公室形成spring data gpm
mongo s inc
蒙哥公司
so you can watch it
这样你就可以看
the rocks constructs was not a place to you
岩石构造对你来说不是一个地方
That's not a lot of the time
这不是很多时间
documentation of the topraks designer
topraks设计师的文档
this is the work out of the box
这是开箱即用的工作
youtube mapping and sword that's it
youtube映射和剑就是这样
much cooks our country's morning and of
煮了我们国家的早晨
course of course we support a classical
当然，我们支持经典
device class for those for the neat
精巧的设备类
working mom and next week but a play
上班妈妈，下个礼拜不过玩
off course motto made public
偏离路线格言公开
but we have not been features at the
但我们尚未成为
for discussions with no public
公开讨论
wafd party that i can use snx
我可以使用snx的wafd派对
alpha version of the car know what you are
这款车的Alpha版知道你是什么
there something that have to wait for
有一些必须等待的东西
active instance demands obama plans to
活动实例要求奥巴马计划
make a release table named with because
制作一个发布表，命名为，因为
only before
仅在之前
like abbott diagnostics and want to go on
像abbott诊断程序一样，想继续
this release as of this date and does
截至该日期的发布，并且
to set the one platform
设置一个平台
behind the organizer like potent hawks
像有力的老鹰一样在组织者后面
josef can dance objectivity because i'm
约瑟夫可以跳舞客观性，因为我
thinking on fertilizer live demo displays
思考肥料现场演示展示
positive tests next week new york
纽约下周进行正面测试
public library for yourself is in the
您自己的公共图书馆在
youtube support very composed but basic
youtube支持非常全面但基本
with pastor i support act like you will
与牧师一起，我支持您的行为
functional in quad at a
四合一功能
functional tmz but is on the client
功能性tmz，但在客户端上
the cypher dsl market it internal causeway
数码单反市场它的内部原因
shifting media change the client in see
转移媒体改变客户
and you will not have it instantly in the
而且您不会立即在
Coop is like that for the crew
船员就像船员一样
how major changes to speak for you could
可以为您代言的重大变化
be easy jet set the desktop 4 and
轻松设置桌面4和
local and since you need to enterprise
本地的，因为你需要企业
version offers the community relations
版本提供社区关系
focus is as long as you want a link to
只要您想要链接到焦点
developing away send boxes cloud instance
开发离开发送盒云实例
of logistics samwer very pleasant care
物流人员的服务非常愉快
build pudding data intelligence data or
建立布丁数据智能数据或
wittling talent festival first
令人兴奋的才艺节
recently is just released a lot of
最近刚刚发布了很多
months ago the new free ebook
几个月前，新的免费电子书
hobby-photographer augsburg fcz is early on
业余摄影师奥格斯堡fcz早
just a fragrance pretty interesting to
只是一种非常有趣的香水
head grafs tufts university backszat
Head grafs Tufts University Backszat
return
回报
[Music]
[音乐]
[Applause]
[鼓掌]
speak now or come to speak
现在说话或说话
light beer database connectivity
轻啤酒数据库连接
[Music]
[音乐]
connected to data is really full
连接到数据真的很满
data in tournament might be or may not
锦标赛中的数据可能会或可能不会
have any benchmarks 100 yards crawl
有任何基准100码爬行
Water is connecting the top teams is
水连接顶级团队
stunned i want connect system on
震惊我想要连接系统
electric onenote wyss of the everywhere
到处都是电子OneNote WYS
Expected so that's ok so first of all
期望如此，所以首先
a still in the mud million and the
一个仍然在泥泞万和
database example it is my bot 5
数据库示例是我的机器人5
million plastic chips machine park 5 million
百万个塑料切片机园区500万个
officially just want to cash flow
正式只是想现金流
Cluster support set mountain passes
集群支持设置山口
protocol as well as it simply continues leader
协议，它只是继续领导
not wide web league some parts europe
不广泛的网络联盟，欧洲部分地区
north carolina to so far so far
北卡罗来纳州到目前为止
developed and collected data centers
开发和收集数据中心
[Music]
[音乐]